// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "Which of the following is an alkaline earth metal?",
        answer: "Calcium",
        options: [
            "Potassium",
            "Lead",
            "Copper",
            "Calcium"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "Double Sulphitation is the most commonly used method in India for refining of _?",
        answer: "Sugar",
        options: [
            "Crude oil",
            "Cooking oils",
            "Sugar",
            "Coal"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "Cooking gas mainly consists of:",
        answer: "Butane and Isobutane",
        options: [
            "Methane and Ethane",
            "Ethylene and carbon monoxide",
            "Butane and Isobutane",
            "Acetylene and hydrogen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "Which among the following acids is generally used as a first hand test to judge whether a metal is Gold or not?",
        answer: "Nitric Acid",
        options: [
            "Sulfuric Acid",
            "Nitric Acid",
            "Hydrochloric Acid",
            "Sulfurous Acid"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "Which of the following alkali metal ions has the highest hydration enthalpy?",
        answer: "Lithium",
        options: [
            "Lithium",
            "Sodium",
            "Potassium",
            "Caesium"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about Hard water?",
        answer: "it does not give lather with soap",
        options: [
            "it is free from soluble salts of calcium and magnesium",
            "it does not give lather with soap",
            "Both a and b",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },


    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "Which of these compounds is also known as wood spirit?",
        answer: "Methanol",
        options: [
            "Ethanol",
            "Methanol",
            "Propanol",
            "None of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "Which of the following is incorrect?",
        answer: "An alloy is a heterogeneous mixture of two or more metals",
        options: [
            "Alloying helps in improving the properties of a meta",
            "An alloy is a heterogeneous mixture of two or more metals",
            "The melting point of an alloy is less than that of pure metals",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "Bell metal is an alloy of which of the following metals?",
        answer: "Copper and Tin",
        options: [
            "Copper and Tin",
            "Copper and Mercury",
            "Copper and Lead",
            "Copper and Zinc"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "Which of the following is correct about suspension?",
        answer: "All of the above",
        options: [
            "It is a heterogeneous mixture",
            "The particles of a suspension can be seen by naked eyes",
            "The particles can be separated from the mixture by the process of filtration",
            "All of the above"
        ]
    },
];